var questionArray = [
  {
    question: "What does SEO stand for?",
    optionsList: [
      "Source Engine Organization",
      "Social Engineer Operator",
      "Search Engine Optimization",
      "Software Engineer Operator",
    ],
    answer: "Search Engine Optimization",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the order for labeling margin and padding?",
    optionsList: ["LBRT", "TRBL", "TBRL", "BTLR"],
    answer: "TRBL",
  },
  {
    question: "Which one is NOT a content model?",
    optionsList: ["heading", "sectioning", "iframe", "flow"],
    answer: "iframe",
  },
  {
    question: "What is used to select an element and apply style to it?",
    optionsList: ["selector", "class", "media query", "inline"],
    answer: "selector",
  },
  {
    question: "How does z-index affect a web page?",
    optionsList: [
      "let's you control main axis",
      "makes it responsive",
      "let's you control the cross axis",
      "allows you to control the depth of objects",
    ],
    answer: "allows you to control the depth of objects",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the difference between an element and and attribute?",
    optionsList: [
      "an element is any tag on your page, an attribute provides details about an element",
      "an attribute is any tag on your page, an element provides details about an attribute",
      " element are found in HTML, attributes are found in CSS",
      " attributes are found in HTML, element are found in CSS",
    ],
    answer:
      "an element is any tag on your page, an attribute provides details about an element",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the 3 main breakpoints?",
    optionsList: [
      "600px, 800px, 1000px",
      "560px, 820px, 975px",
      "575px, 768px, 980px",
      "500px, 700px, 900px",
    ],
    answer: "575px, 768px, 980px",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a code block?",
    optionsList: [
      "code on HTML",
      "code between curly braces",
      "code in blocks",
      "code between quotations",
    ],
    answer: "code between curly braces",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is a plain language description of the steps that an algorithm or application must complete?",
    optionsList: ["expression", "condition", "declaration", "pseudocode"],
    answer: "pseudocode",
  },
  {
    question: "What is a data structure designed to store data?",
    optionsList: ["array", "object", "primitive data", "arguments"],
    answer: "array",
  },
];
